Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
（計(けい)）ハァハァ…
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
One dead.
（西(にし)）１名死亡 決定
（計）ウ… ウワッ！
This can't be happening...
（計）ウソだろう？
What do I do?
おい どうする？
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
Yuzo?
What do I do?
どうすんだよ？ どうする？ おい！
What am I supposed to do?
ハァ ハァ ハァ…
Don't come! Don't come this way!
来るな！ こっち来んな！
Please wait
for the light.
Don't come! Don't come this way!
Change!
変われ！ 信号 早く変われ！
Light, come on, change!
Get a grip, Kei.
落ち着け 俺！
…んな物(もん)で止まるわけねえだろう
You know this won't stop that damn thing!
It... it stopped. All right...
と… 止まってんじゃん　ラッキー
Hey, don't ignore the lights!
し… し… 信号無視すんな！
Kishimoto, I'm gonna die.
岸本(きしもと) 俺 死んじゃうよ
もうダメだ…
This is it!
アア… 何だ？ こいつ　気持ち悪い
What the hell is this thing?
He's freaking me out!
あれ？
Huh?
What happened?
なんでだ？ もしかして
俺 あいつに見えてないのか？
Could it be that he can't see me?
Then maybe I can get him.
If it's from behind...
だったら やれるか？ 後ろからなら
Do I do it? Could I get him?
やるか？ やれるか？
I can end it right here, right now.
そうだ 俺が早めに終わらせてやる
The thing's just a robot,
no matter how you look at it!
あれ どう見てもロボットだもんな
If it's only a robot...
ロボットなら… ロボットなら…
What the hell?
（計）何だ？ これ　骨… 骨がある
Bones? He's got bones!
Now what? This thing must be alive!
どうしよう　こいつ 生き物だ
What do I do now?
どうしよう　でっけえ生き物
殺したことねえもんな
I've never killed anything this big before.
（計）あの中坊は どうかしてんだ
There's just something wrong with that kid!
Damn it, I can't do this.
やっぱ できねえ
Yuzo?
（鈴木(すずき)星人）裕三(ゆうぞう)君？
（計）はぁ？
Huh?
Yuzo?
（鈴木星人）裕三君？
Yuzo...
I'm not Yuzo.
違います
Kantaro, yeah!
かんたろー はい
What?
Kantaro! Okay, all together now!
（鈴木星人）
“かんたろー”と　はい 一緒に
（欣二(きんじ)）オッ…
（春哉(はるや)）アア…
（カヨ）ここ どこかしら？
Where are we?
Yes, we did it! We're outside, Grandma!
（亮太(りょうた)）
やった！ 外だ おばあちゃん
You're right.
そうね　これで 帰れるわね
I guess we can go home now.
Wait a minute please!
（加藤(かとう)）ちょっと待ってください
（亮太）うん？
Everyone, please come over here.
（加藤）みんな 集まってくれ
（春哉）帰るっつうの バ～カ！
（欣二）あいつ 何か言ってるぜ
Hey, I'm outta here, dumbass!
He's mumbling something.
Stop right there.
（鉄男(てつお)）待てや こら
Huh?
You planning to just leave
Kosuke's body there like that?
（鉄男）康介(こうすけ)の死体
あのままにしとくのかよ？
So go dig him a grave or something.
てめえで墓でも掘れよ　知るか
You think I give a shit?
Anyway I gotta run.
逃げるっきゃねえ
とりあえず
みんなんとこ行くしか…
I have to go where everyone is.
Kantaro!
かんたろー！
Kato!
加藤！
あっ… 計ちゃん
It's Kei.
Hey, isn't that...
（岸本）ねえ あれ…
（加藤）あっ…
（鉄男）あれか 何とか星人
Is that it?
The whatever-alien...
Yeah, that's it.
そ… そうだ
何だ？ ありゃ
What the hell's that thing supposed to be?
欣二 もうちょっと いようか
面白そうだからよ
Kinji, wanna stick around a little longer?
This looks like it could get interesting.
（亮太）おばあちゃん ロボットだ
Grandma! That's a robot!
That's a pretty good robot.
（北条(ほうじょう)）よくできてんな
Kurono...
玄野(くろの)君…
Sweet! She was worried about me!
うれちー
一応 心配してくれてたんだ？
So you couldn't get rid of him?
やっつけられなかったの？
Is that all she cares about?
そっちの心配かよ
Stay back, everyone!
（加藤）みんな 近寄るな！
あっ 機嫌直ってる
He doesn't look angry anymore.
Well, what do we do now, Kato?
どうする？ 加藤
Will you look at this crap?
What the hell kind of alien is that?
何だよ？ こいつ
どこが宇宙人だっての？
You know, even motorcycle companies
are making robots these days.
バイク屋とかさ
最近 ロボット作ってるだろう
あれだよ あれ
I'll bet that thing's one of 'em!
Can I go now?
（北条）帰っていいか？
Whoa, hold on.
（加藤）ちょ… ちょっと
待ってくれ　帰るのは待ってくれ
Don't go just yet.
Kei, is this thing dangerous or what?
計ちゃん こいつ 危険そうか？
I dunno.
分かんねえけど
ネギ星人のときとか思い出したら…
But if you remember that Green onion Alien...
Green onion Alien?
ネギ星人？
Huh?
はぁ？
吉田(よしだ)の前はネギだったのかよ？
What, you fought a green onion before Yoshida?
What kinda bullshit is that?
バッカじゃねえの？
It's SUZUKI! This is the Suzuki Alien!
鈴木だ！ 鈴木星人！
So what are you saying?
それで？
（計）あっ…
Well...
ガンツが ネギ星人って
紹介したのは―
You remember how when Gantz introduced
the Green onion Alien to us,
The Green onion Alien
Traits:
Strong,
smelly
Likes:
Green onions,
friendship
You remember how when Gantz introduced
the Green onion Alien to us,
The Green onion Alien
Traits:
Strong,
smelly
Likes:
Green onions,
friendship
it showed us the wimpy little one?
It showed us the wimpy little one?
あの小さくて
弱そうなヤツだったろう？
But then...
でも…
もしかしたら もう１匹
強いのが いるかもしれない
So maybe there could be another
strong one like him.
C'mon, man!
おいおい お前ら
Can't you even make up your damn minds
about kicking this stupid robot's ass?
こんなしょうもないロボット
やるの やらないのって…
Jeez, you two got some serious problems.
やっぱり どうかしてるぜ
欣二 行こうぜ　腹減った
Kinji, let's get out of here. I'm hungry.
Yeah, why don't we go get some ramen?
ああ ラーメン屋行くか？
（春哉）そうだな
Good call.
Yeah, why don't we go get some ramen?
I'll be damned if you're coming along with us!
てめえは絶対 誘わねえ
Ryota, do you wanna go now?
亮太 そろそろ行こうか
（亮太）イヤだ！
No way! This robot looks cool.
このロボット 面白いもん！
Oh dear...
困ったね
早く お母さんのお家(うち)に行かないと
But we have to get you back
to your mother soon.
どこかに公衆電話ないかしらねえ
I wonder if there's a payphone nearby?
Damn!
That little shit...
あのガキ…
中坊 お前 また隠れてたな
この卑怯者(ひきょうもん)！
So you've been hiding again, huh?
You little coward!
Ah, shut up. Now get outta the way!
うるさい　どけ！
ウワッ！
（岸本）ちょ… ちょっと！
Hey, don't hide behind me!
私の後ろに隠れないでよ！
What am I supposed to do?
I'm not wearing a suit or anything!
（計）しょうがねえだろう
俺 丸裸なんだから！
自分だって いつも
加藤の後ろに隠れてるだろうが
Aren't you always hiding behind Kato, anyway?
Ten more points...
あと10点
（計）えっ？
Ten more points...
あと10点
（加藤）あっ… やめろ 西！
Don't do it, Nishi!
（欣二）うわ！ 飛んだ飛んだ
Whoa! The thing can fly!
（春哉）ハハハッ…
あれ どういう仕掛けよ？
How did it do that?
This is starting to look really bad.
これ マジで やべえぞ
おばあちゃん 見て　飛んだよ！
Grandma! Look! It's flying!
Can I go home now?
帰っていいか？
Yeah, whatever...
まあ いいや　来いよ
Come on!
He disappeared!
消えたぜ…
（北条）もうちょっと いようかな
I think I'm gonna stay a little longer.
Okay, all together!
さあ 一緒に！
What the hell is that robot doing?!
（鉄男）
何やってんだ？ あのロボット
That was Nishi just now, wasn't it?
今の中坊だよな？
I think so...
そうだと思う
あのロボットには見えるらしい
Seems that robot can see him after all.
Grandma!
おばあちゃん
あそこ壊れちゃったよ
Look at all that stuff it destroyed! Wow!
すっごい
（カヨ）あっ…
It saw him that time, didn't it?
やっぱり 今見えたよな？
（加藤）うん
Yeah...
ねえ 見て おばあちゃん
Look, Grandma!
That guy can disappear, too! That's so cool!
あのおにいちゃん
消えたりできるんだ？
カッコイイ！
（カヨ）そうね
Uh, yeah...
That little shit!
あのガキ
なんで あんなことできるんだ？
How come he can do stuff like that?!
I don't know!
分からない　ガンツに聞いてくれ
Why don't you ask Gantz?
Gantz?
ガンツ？ 何だ？ そりゃ
What the hell is that?
We don't really know.
よく分かんねえけど
なんかムカつくヤツだよ
It's one annoying son of a bitch though.
Damn!
What the fuck!
なんだよ？ 今度は消えねえじゃん
He ain't disappearing no more!
C'mon, kid! Do your little trick again!
おらおら ガキ！
また手品見せてみろや！
Ten more points...
あと10点… あと10点なんだよ！
Ten more points, damn it!
Stop running away! Just give up!
逃げんな！ おとなしく…
かんたろー！
くそ…
Shit!
Hey, do you think that thing is broken?
He stopped disappearing.
（岸本）ねえ
あれ 壊れちゃったんじゃないの？
消えなくなっちゃったよ
That thing could see him anyway,
so it makes no difference!
（計）どうせ 相手には見えてんだ
関係ねえよ
Kei, you might be right, but still...
（加藤）
計ちゃん それは そうだけど…
あんなヤツ…
To hell with that little shit!
Hey, what are you all gawking at?
なに見てんだ お前(めえ)ら！ 手伝え！
Help me out here!
Hey, did you hear that, Haruya?
春哉 今の聞いた？
…たく 世の中
分かってねえのは どっちだか
Heh, who's the one that doesn't get it now?
You can go to Hell!
死ね！
お前
俺らのことゴミって言ったよな？
You're the one who called us
garbage before! Remember?
So do you beg garbage for help
when things get bad?
ヤバくなると
ゴミにまで泣き入れんのかよ？
We'd love to help you, but we can't since
we're garbage and all. Get it?
（欣二）どうせゴミだからよ
手伝うったって何もできねえわけよ
分かる？
（春哉）分かる？
Yeah, ya get it?
ギャハハッ…
（欣二）ハハハッ…
Whoo boy! Your peashooter's gone!
（春哉）おお おお
拳銃(ハジキ)がなくなっちゃったよ
Now what are you gonna do, ya little shit?
さあさあ どうする？ そこのガキ
Just shut up and help me now!
（西）いいから 早く手伝え！
ざけんな てめえ！
さんざん俺たちバカにしやがって
Don't give me that crap!
After all the shit you gave us earlier!
You can just stay there and
fucking die! DIE! DIE!
そのまま死ね！ 死ね！ 死ね！
冗談じゃねえぜ
Give me a break!
お前
みんな 死んでるって言ったよな？
You told us we're all dead anyway, right?
So what difference does it make?
だったら関係ねえじゃん
何回でも死んでみろや
You can just keep on dying
and dying, right? Huh?
ああ？ こら！
Haruya, that's enough.
（鉄男）春哉 その辺にしとけ
Shut up.
うるせえ！ てめえは黙って…
You stay out of...
My fuckin' tooth!
（欣二）鉄ちゃん 何すんだよ？
Tetsu, what the hell did you do that for?
Thugs certainly love knocking
each other's teeth out.
ヤンキーって 歯折んの好きだよな
Hey, kid! Looks like this isn't just a game, is it?
ガキ どうも
ただのゲームじゃなさそうだな
I get the idea you're in a lot of trouble right now.
お前がヤバそうなのも
なんとなく分かるぜ
But you still did blow Kosuke's head off!
けどな てめえ
康介の頭 吹っ飛ばしてんだぞ！
I hope you didn't forget about that!
それ忘れてねえよな？
You murdered another person!
人１人 殺したんだぞ てめえは！
Tell us something to show that you're sorry!
ひと言くらい わび入れろや！
There's nothing more disgusting than
a murderer beggin' for his own life!
人殺しが命ごいするほど―
みっともねえことは ねえんだぜ
ああ？
You hear me?
Well say something!
どうなんだ！
You gonna apologize for blowing
Kosuke's head off or not?
“康介の頭 吹っ飛ばして
ごめんなさい”ってな
ひと言でも
わびる気あんのか ないのか
Are you going to show any remorse at all? Well?
どっちなんだ！ ああ？
Wait!
（計）待てよ！
（鉄男）ああ？
What?!
Are you gonna help the little shit
if he does apologize?
謝ったら助けんのかよ？
あんなヤツ
何言ってんだ？ てめえ
What the hell are you saying?
Kurono?
玄野君？
（加藤）計ちゃん…
Kei...
He's just trying to save his own ass.
あいつな
１人だけ生き残ろうとしてんだよ
いっつもな
The only thing he's ever cared about
is his damned score.
てめえの点数のことしか
考えてないんだ
Are you willing to help a guy like that?
そんなヤツ…
そんなヤツ 助けんのかよ？
This is about taking moral responsibility.
けじめだよ けじめ
I'm not like your frickin' indecisive leader.
俺は どっかの
優柔不断なリーダーとは違うからよ
Do any of you...
お前ら…
（鉄男）
命とかって分かってんのかよ？
...understand the preciousness of life?
Do you?
（鉄男）分かってんのかよ？
I'm not saying I completely believe him.
But at this rate, that kid's gonna die.
まだ完全に
信じたわけじゃねえけどな
あのガキ 多分 このままだと死ぬぜ
So what are you going to do? Well?
どうするよ？ ああ？
Don't get me wrong.
だからってな 俺だって
人殺しをそう簡単に助ける気はねえ
That doesn't mean that I'm going to
save murderers so easily either.
But I might consider it only if he apologizes.
あいつが わび入れたら
考えないこともねえ
He's treated all of us like shit. I'm no exception.
お前ら あいつに さんざん
ひでえこと言われたろう？
俺だって そうだ
But I don't really mind helping him
so long as he apologizes.
けどな 俺は わびのひと言聞ければ
助けてもいいと思ってる
What about you three?
さあ どうする？
Somebody!
誰か 助けろ！ 助けてくれ！
Help!
Help me!
助けろ！
What the...
な… 何だ？
あいつ どうしたんだ？
What's happening to him?
My suit...
スーツが…
スーツがオシャカになった！
My suit is no good now!
Hey, Grandma, what's wrong with him?
おばあちゃん ねえ
あのおにいちゃん どうしたの？
（カヨ）見ちゃダメよ
Don't look.
Huh? Why?
えっ？ どうして？
（カヨ）
また死ぬかもしれないからね
Because he might die again.
What do you mean?
（亮太）なに？ それ
Goddammit, APOLOGIZE!
Listen to me, you little shit!
謝れ！ おい ガキ！
Well how about it?
（鉄男）どうなんだ？ ああ？
If anyone points a gun at me...
（西）俺に銃を向けたヤツは…
I'll kill 'em!
ソッコー殺す！ 絶対 謝んねえ！
I will never apologize!
That son of a bitch...
（鉄男）あのクソガキ…
Help...
助けてくれ　誰か… 助け…
Somebody help me, help.
Why can't you just say you're sorry?
なんで謝んねえんだよ！
加藤
（岸本）加藤君？
Kato!
Kato...
命なんて よく分かってねえけど…
（鉄男）うん？
I don't know much about life, but...
Look, we're all going to go back together.
（加藤）
とにかく みんなで帰るんだ
He can apologize anytime!
謝るのなんて いつでもできる
計ちゃん
スーツの使い方 教えてくれ！
Kei, tell me how to use this suit.
（加藤）あいつが死んだら
本当に何も分からなくなる
If he dies, nobody will be able to
tell us what's going on!
てめえ あんなヤツ 助けんのかよ？
What the hell?!
You're gonna help that son of a bitch?
Kato, you can't do it!
加藤君 ムリよ
あの子でも やられそうなのよ
Even Nishi's on the verge of getting killed!
Kato, I don't think this is a good idea.
加藤 ヤ… ヤバイって…
使い方は？
How do I use this?
とにかく 気合い入れれば
なんとかなるけど…
Well, you should be okay as
long as you focus, but...
Thanks.
ありがとう
あのさ 計ちゃん
You know what, Kei?
（計）な… 何だよ？
What?
いちばん帰りたいの…
The one who wants to go home the most...
...is me.
俺なんだよね
（計）あっ…
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
Grandma, what's that guy doing?
（亮太）
おばあちゃん あの人 何してるの？
Huh? He disappeared!
あっ 消えたよ
Now he's being shot!
He's gonna die, Grandma!
あっ なんか撃たれてるよ
死んじゃうよ おばあちゃん
次回 “あいつは撃てない”
Next episode: "He Can't Shoot"